Marc Tucker

Student, Software Developer

02/09/2016

PROFILE

I am a 22-year-old student, currently in my final year of my bachelor's degree at the Auckland University of Technology. I have always been immensely passionate about analysing and creating solutions to new problems. I enjoy spending any of my spare time programming, developing games or improving my fitness. I am also a highly motivated, outgoing and friendly individual that is dedicated to providing quality work, with excellent team skills.

CONTACT



marcedforlife@gmail.com



021 029 08256



205/207 Federal Street, Auckland 1010

SKILLSET

Languages:

- Java
- C++
- SQL
- HTML
- PHP
- Javascript

Software:

- Eclipse
- Visual Studio
- Android Studio
- Photoshop
- Heidi

EDUCATION

Auckland University of Technology / Bachelor of Computer Information Sciences

March 2013 - PRESENT, Auckland

Currently completing my third and final year of my bachelors in computer information sciences majoring in software development.

Kerikeri High School / NCEA Level 3

February 2011 - November 2012, Kerikeri

Where I completed my final year of high school study.

WORK EXPERIENCE

New World Metro / Checkout Operator

July 2015 - PRESENT, Auckland

I currently work two small shifts per week at New World Metro to help assist me financially while I study.

New World Kerikeri/ Checkout Operator, Supervisor

February 2012 - February 2016, Kerikeri

My initial role at New World Kerikeri was a checkout operator, however I was quickly promoted to a supervisor role and was entrusted to look after/manage large teams among various other duties. The timeframe includes the two previous Summer breaks from University.

Kerikeri Bakehouse / Cafe Worker

October 2011 - February 2012, Kerikeri

This was my first place of part-time employment while still attending high school.